rewardscenter.net 2011-09-03

# Rewards Center

**This privacy policy updated October 26, 2009**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**   
This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use your personal information in connection with our advertising, content, e-commerce, promotional and service programs and other business activities (the "Program") and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services and the sites of our advertisers.

**What Information We Collect**   
When you visit our site we may collect two types of information: (a) personal information you actively choose to disclose and (b) information about you that is collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties in a way not visible to you.

  * (a) _Information you actively choose to provide._ By choosing to participate in our Program, you must become a Member by disclosing the following information, such as: your email address, name, address, phone number and birth date. During the process of registering on our site, participating in various offers, completing surveys, or sending us emails or correspondence, we collect additional information that you may disclose, including for example mobile telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address), credit information, social security number, health information and personal preferences regarding lifestyle, products or services.
  * (b) _Passive information collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties._ We collect some information about you simply by virtue of you connecting to our web site. Our servers automatically identify your computer by its internet protocol ("IP") address, a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. In addition, to participate in our program you must allow cookies to be active on your system. Cookies are a feature of web browser software (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, etc.) that allows web servers to recognize which computer is used to access a web site. Cookies simplify subsequent interactions on our site and streamline your transactions on related web pages. Information collected through cookies may include the date and time of your visits, the site pages you viewed, the time spent at each page, and the web sites you visited just before and just after our site. You can disable the cookie function by following the instructions in the "help" section of your browser. However, doing so will likely make it impossible for our system to properly recognize you when you visit our sites, and consequently may make your participation in our program more difficult or impossible. In addition to the information you provide or that is collected automatically from our system, we may obtain information about you from our marketing partners or other third parties, and we combine that information with the information you actively provide or that is automatically collected by our servers.

The term "Information" is used in this policy to refer to both types of information described above, as well as any Information that you provide to us directly by phone (including any phone number displayed via caller ID), text or SMS message, U.S. mail or through any other written or oral communication with us.

**Use of Data Collected**

**OPT-IN NOTICE: By Participating, You Expressly "Opt In" To Receive Information And Grant Us Permission To Share Your Information**   
By signing up for our Program you expressly opt in to receive future information about products and services from us and from a variety of advertisers to whom we may provide your Information. We will share your personal information with third parties for any reason we choose, including without limitation for the following purposes: (1) to operate our Program (including the transfer of the information to advertisers or to third parties who maintain on our behalf a list of persons having registered with our Program), (2) to permit advertisers or other third parties to use your Information for any purpose such as contacting you by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication for any purpose, (3) to confirm you have completed all of the necessary steps to receive your gift, and (4) as we are required to do by law, including to notify the IRS that you received your gift. As a result, we will transfer your Information to third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control.  
In addition, in the event we consider a transaction involving the purchase or sale of our assets or stock, other companies may review our records, including your Information, to make business decisions about the transaction. Likewise, your Information may be transferred to third parties in the event of the sale or acquisition of our company or any of its assets. The parties who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant banks, our internet service provider, etc.) also may have access to your information in performing their services.

**Special Note About Information You Provide Directly To Our Advertisers.**   
You are able to access certain advertiser's sites through our site. When you opt to receive information or sign up for an offer from an advertiser, you may be doing so through third party sites and with other companies over which we have no control. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you wish to opt out of those advertisers' mailings, you must do so directly with such advertisers or as otherwise provided on or through their sites.

**Third Party Ad Servers.**   
We may serve advertisements within our Web Site either ourselves or by allowing other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to do so. In addition, some of our advertisers may use the services of third-party ad networks. Some of these third-party ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the third-party ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, third-party ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows a third-party ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or third-party ad networks. Those third-party ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting. You may find more information at the web site of either the individual third-party ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative (http://www.networkadvertising.org). 

**Security Of Your Information.**   
We use reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Information. However, nearly all Internet transmissions pass through many servers not controlled by us, and therefore we cannot guarantee that any information you provide us or we collect will not be intercepted or altered in that process. Also, as noted above, your Information is shared with third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control. 

**How You Can Choose To "Opt Out" Of Receiving Further Information About Products Or Services**  
If at any time you do not wish to receive further information about products or services from us and wish us to cease providing your Information to third parties, you may chose to "opt-out" through the Unsubscribe/"Opt-Out" page of our site or by written request sent by U.S. mail to our Customer Service Manager at the following address:

RewardsCenter.net  
221 N. La Salle St  
Suite 1612    
Chicago, IL 60601 

We will promptly update our records upon receiving your clear instructions to opt-out, but it may take up to ten (10) business days from our receipt of your request for the change to be fully effective. If you later give us a clear statement that you want to receive emails from us or our advertisers after such date, then that opt-in statement will supersede any earlier opt-out request. If we have already provided your email address or other information to an advertiser or other third party before we receive your opt-out request, we cannot prevent them from sending or continuing to send you information or emails and you will need to contact such third party directly.

**SMS Offering and Opt-out rights**  
By completing or submitting a registration form or partial registration form you are consenting to receive SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove your information by replying  "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request. This website, websites linking to this website, and websites linked from this website (collectively "We") may make available a service either directly or through third parties by which you can receive commercial messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). Your provider's standard data and messaging rates apply to all SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS Service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. The use of this information will be in accordance with this Mobile Policy. 

If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies. You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. You may opt out of the SMS Service at any time by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. This process impacts only the future delivery of the particular SMS message offering, so you must send that message for each offering. 

**How To Correct, Delete Or Access Your Information**   
If you wish to access, delete or correct the information you have provided to us through this site, please contact us through the Contact Us section of our site or through written request sent by U.S. mail to the Customer Service Manager at the address listed above.

**Special Rights For Residents Of Certain States**   
If you are a California resident or another state with specific laws relating to the collection and use of Information, you may have specific rights not set forth in this policy. For example, California residents have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name registration (email address), the site name you visited and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please mail your request to Customer Service Manager at the address listed in the footer of this site or the Contact Us page.

PLEASE CHECK THIS PRIVACY POLICY PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES AS WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. SUCH REVISIONS TO THE PRIVACY POLICY SHALL TAKE EFFECT WHEN POSTED. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR SERVICES THROUGH ANY COMMUNICATION CHANNEL FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES. 

RewardsCenter.net has not received any consideration from any of the above entities nor is RewardsCenter.net affiliated or associated with them in any way. To claim your reward you must participate in our program and meet all of the offer eligibility requirements as outlined in the Terms & Conditions.

Copyright © 2009 RewardsCenter.net - RewardsCenter.net is an independent rewards program and is not affiliated with the above entities or other advertisers that may appear on our network. Trademarks, service marks, logos, and/or domain names (including, without limitation, the individual names of products and retailers) are the property of their respective owners, who have no association with or make any endorsement of the products or services provided by RewardsCenter.net. If you have any questions regarding this offer, please review our help section or contact us by clicking here. By submitting I agree that I may receive email and SMS offers from Rewards Center and third party marketers.
